

MOHAMMED ALSHAKHOORI

JOB SEEKER

Career Objective

Motivated accounting graduate with a deep knowledge in accounting, auditing and corporate finance seeks obtaining Accountant position at a reputable organization which will benefit from my strong skills. Furthermore, will help me in getting the experience needed to implement my major studies, improveing my skills, and to achive organizational objectives.

Skills

- Tally ERP9
- Team work
- Good Communication skills
- Microsoft Office
- Time Management
- Decision Making

Contact

Address:

Villa 1961, Road 931, Block 1209, Hamad Town.

Phone:

+973 32333517

Email:

Moh22994@gmail.com

CPR:

940907844

Languages

✓ Arabic: Native

✓ English: Very good

Experience

Accountant at Sehab Travel Establishment - 02/2020 to 01/2021

- Verify, allocate, post and reconcile accounts receivable.
- Posting the details of the company receipts & invoices and other documents in the accounting software.
- Work with senior accountant to solve financial discrepancies by collecting and analyzing account information.

Sales Agent at Mohammed Ali Asghar Trading - 11/2017 to 02/2020

- Present, promote and sell products using negotiation with existing and prospective customers.
- Dealing with multiple purchasing department officers from different companies to build a sustainable relationship.
- Collecting the local purchase orders and cheques from customers.

Accounts Trainee at Northern Area Municipality - 07/2016 to 08/2016

- Posting and processing journal entries to ensure all transactions are recorded.
- Assist senior accountants in preparation of monthly reports.
- Update financial data in databases to ensure that information will be accurate and available when needed.

Hobbies

- ✓ Internet Browsing
- ✓ Reading
- ✓ Sport

Education

Bachelor of Science: Collage of Business Administration, Accounting 2017 University of Bahrain, Sakhair.

Certifications

ALJESR training workshop certificate - 2017 Bahrain Society for Training
& Development.

References

Available upon request.